Poppers-Bating I
Rules:
Eyes on the screen
Follow my instructions
Sniff poppers on command
Cum only at the end when allowed
Stroke yourself hard!
Soon we'll start!
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
One very deep inhale.
Hold.
Exhale.
Here we go!
Show me your cock
And now stroke along in the rhythm!
Stand completely nude and show me your hot cock
This is now YOUR cock!
And your thick balls
And the thick balls
Stroke it
Stroke yourself thoroughly
Smack, smack, smack, up to the hilt!
Thoroughly stroke your thick cock
Yeeees, hot!
Show it to me
Show me your dick
Show me your rod
Yeah, stroke your hot rod
Ram it in!
Make yourself as horny as possible
Stroke the fuck rod
So warm and tight
Stroke the fuck rod thoroughly
I'm looking at your giant dick
Your dick is hot
Imagine how it feels
to to cum in the pussy
jerk, jerk, jerk with every stroke
Stroke it thorough
Horny whore
hot filthy stroke whore
That's what you are
You are my stroke whore
Stroke yourself
Horny
Go on, ram it like you mean it
I want you to come slowly
From the hips!
Slowly
Stroke yourself up
Filthy horny whore
Stroke yourself
Stroke your cock
Are you horny enough for the next round of poppers yet?
You can handle a few more thrusts!
I'll let you fuck
I'll let you fuck thoroughly
Your cock is so hot.
But soon it will get even hotter!
I fuck you
You know I need your thick cock
So make it thick
Show it to me
Your cock is so hot.
But soon it will get even hotter!
Hold it in front of my face
In front
of my
face
Did you understand that?
And jerk-off like a horny pig
Horny stroke pig
Like a stroke pig that's getting milked.
Fuck it a few more times!
and fucked and fucked
You are getting fucked
Now comes round 2
You whore. You whore. You whore
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
Deep inhale!
Hold!
Exhale
Keep stroking to the rhythm while poppers fuck up your brain
Eyes on the tits!
Forget everything else!
There is nothing else besides
stroking and tits!
Think about cuming.
Imagine it.
You are getting fucked so hard.
You want to take those tits in your hand!
You want to cum inside her!
Eversy thrust makes you hornier!
You want to cum.
But you mustn't cum!
You are now ready for the next brainfuck.
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
Deep inhale!
Keep holding!
Keep holding further!
Exhale!
Now continue stroking very slowly.
Look exacrly how this pussy jerks.
You litle cock whore.
Did you hear?
Now comes the orgasm!
That's what you are
A little cock whore
And stroke yourself
Stroke faster!
But don't cum!
Your cock will now get as horny as her pussy!
Hotter and hotter
I want to fuck you
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Feel it cumming!
... and ...
Stroke slowly!
Do it whore
Squeeze your hand when she jerks!
Stroke yourself
The orgasm is comming!
Attention!
I'm fucking you
Squeeze!
You horny pig
And again! Until the next brainfuck!
Stroke yourself
Squeeze
Fuck me
Fuck me you horny piece of filth
Yeees, very nice.
Now you're ready for the next round!
Attention! Prepare your poppers!
One very deep inhale.
(1/2)
Hold.
Exhale.
Inahle again deeply.
(2/2)
Hold.
Exhale
Stroke along again to the rhythm!
Let it slap you horny stallion!
Fuck your hand
The mares want to be mated!
And stroke yourself
Stroke yourself
Push her down!
You whore
Fuckwhore
Look how he urges to cum!
Horny slut
He wants to fill her up with his sperm!
cock slut
Now think about your penis!
cock whore
Imagine you'd be allowed to cum like him!
Stroke yourself you cock whore
Your hand is this pussy.
So hot.
Rub yourself
little perverted cock whore
If you manage not to cum, you may proceed to the next round!
rub the whore cock
Soon comes the cumshot!
In with the sperm!
and now stroke yourself
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
One very deep inahle.
(1/2)
Hold
Continue holding
Inhale deeply again
(2/2)
Hold.
Exhale
Let the rush come over you!
Stroke in the rhythm!
Feel your cock betweeen her hot tits!
Up and down! So hot!
Thrust between the hot tits!
Don't forget your glans!
Your glans rubs between the tits!
Your brain is melting!
Thrust! Thrust! Thrust! Cum!
Penis. Tits. Glans. Tits.
Rubbing! Thrusting! Moaning!
Stroke yourself superfast with two fingers!
Penis. Tits. Glans. Tits
Just don't cum!
Soon you're done!
Just one more round!
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
One very deep inhale.
(1/3)
Hold.
Exhale.
Again deep inhale.
(2/3)
Hold.
Keep holding.
Keep on holding.
Exhale.
Stroke to the beat!
Your head is spinning!
Your ears are ringing!
Your heart is racing!
Thrust deep into the pusy!
Pump! Pump! Pump!
Your orgasm will shatter your brain!
Oh god how hot!
When will he finaly cum into that hot pussy?
Can you hold out until then?
Oh god i think he'll come soon!
You must not come!
Hands off!
Stop stroking!
Attention!
Prepare your poppers!
One very deep inhale.
(1/3)
Hold.
Exhale.
Again deep inhale.
(2/3)
Hold.
Keep holding.
Exhale
And a third deep inhale
(3/3)
Hold
Keep holding
Exhale.
Enjoy your last rush
Soon you may cum!
Go on, stroke and fill her up!